hobbyeasy.com 2010-12-29

# Privacy Policy

|  **Privacy Policy**  

* * *

**Hobbyeasy** takes your privacy concerns very seriously, and confirm to users of this site that we will not sell or lease individual user information to others and will only share information in accordance with this privacy policy. 

Protecting your privacy is very important to us and we take this responsibility very seriously. Personal information, such as name, address, telephone number, and email address, are collected by **Hobbyeasy** for the normal processing of your order. Credit card account information is used for the sole purpose of processing your current order and is never distributed to persons outside of the processing service.

"Cookies" are used to track Internet session information so that we can distinguish your order from others in our on-line order processing system.

If you prefer that your name and address are not shared with other parties, please advise our Customer Service department of your wishes at [privacy@hobbyeasy.com](mailto:privacy@hobbyeasy.com)

**How We Use Your Information**  
We use the information that we collect from you to process your requests, to provide an enhanced and more personalised experience, and to inform you of our new offers and features. We will use aggregate and non-personally identifying information for purposes that we deem necessary. For instance, we will use this non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website(s) and to share with advertisers for marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these instances, we do not disclose anything that could be used to identify you. We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described below without providing you an opportunity to opt-in or opt-out of such operations.

Please be aware that when you click on any advertising banners that may appear on our website(s) that take you to third-party websites, you will be subject to the their privacy policies and not ours. While we support the protection of privacy on our website(s), we cannot be responsible for the actions of third parties. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement prior to providing any personal information to and/or interacting with any other website(s).

We will use your information to provide our services to you. As a part of our services, we will communicate via e-mail, postal mail, and/or other means to inform you of enhancements or changes in offers, services or other relevant information targeted to your interests. These communications may include third-party marketing messages, but your personally identifying information will not be provided to such parties as we are communicating with you direct. We expect to make several mailings throughout the year to let you know about new services or to notify you of service changes.

The information you provide may be used by us to target more relevant and specific messages to you. These electronic messages may include promotional offers from carefully screened third parties and advertising sponsors. (Please note that this does not refer to any banner advertisements on our website(s).) In doing so, we are providing you with information on behalf of other businesses, but do not make your personally identifying information available to such third parties. If you do not want to receive such offers, you may opt-out at your convenience.

End of page |
